psp-themes.net 2012-03-22

# Privacy Policy - PSP Themes

Privacy Policy - PSP Themes   

* * *

This notice provides PSP-Themes' policy regarding the nature, purpose, use and sharing of any information collected via this Web site. 

Submitting information is strictly voluntary. By doing so, you are giving PSP-Themes.net your permission to use the information for the intended purpose. 

There are several types of information we collect. These include: 

Automatically Collected Information  
We collect and temporarily store certain technical information about your visit for use in site management and security purposes. This information includes:   
The date and time you access PSP-Themes.net  
The URLs of the pages you visit  
The Internet domain from which you access PSP-Themes.net.  
The IP address from which you access PSP-Themes.net  
The type of browser used to access our site.  
The operating system used to access our site.  
If you visited this Web site from another Web site, the URL of the forwarding site.  
This information is only used to help us make our site more useful for you. With this data we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. 

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are retained temporarily as required for security and site management purposes only. 

Cookies  
PSP-Themes.net Web sites may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site. 

At no time is your private information, whether stored in persistent cookies or elsewhere, shared with third parties who have no right to that information. If you do not wish to have session or persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>. 

Personal Information  
If you choose to provide us with personal information, through such methods as completing a form or sending us an email, we will use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information or services you have requested. 

Accessibility Statement  
We continually strive to ensure the pages on this Web site are accessible to individuals with disabilities in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act. If you have any difficulty viewing any page with adaptive technology, please contact the webmaster. 

Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement  
PSP-Themes.net links to many Web sites. PSP-Themes.net provides links to these sites as a service to our users. The presence of a link is not a PSP-Themes.net endorsement of the site. 

When users follow a link to an outside Web site, they are leaving PSP-Themes.net and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the owners/sponsors of the outside Web site(s). PSP-Themes.net is not responsible for the information collection practices of those sites.
